https://www.weyerhaeuser.com/privacy/ccpa/

Welcome to Weyerhaeuser's new website!
You appear to be using an older browser. This website is best viewed using the latest versions of Internet Explorer, Chrome, Safari, and Firefox. If you proceed without upgrading or switching browsers, you may not experience optimal navigation or page functionality. Thank you for your interest in Weyerhaeuser and we hope you enjoy your visit.
Update my browser now
×
Timberlands
Timberlands
Trees are a remarkable resource that, when managed responsibly, can meet a wide range of fundamental needs for people and the planet for generations to come.
Learn More
Forestry
Sustainable Forestry
Western U.S. Forests
Southern U.S. Forests
Northern U.S. Forests
Canadian Forests
Log Sales
Recreation
With millions of acres across the U.S., we offer hunters, anglers and other outdoor enthusiasts a vast resource for enjoying outdoor recreation.
Learn More
Find A Lease
Search Leases
Lease FAQs
Campsite Program
Food Plot Program
Sample Leases
Newsletters
Land
We’re one of the largest private landholders in the United States. As stewards of these assets, we maximize the value of every acre.
Learn More
Real Estate
Development Projects
Aggregates
Minerals
Conservation
Mitigation Banking
Bank Information
Wood Products
Wood Products
We’ve been developing new building products and solutions for more than 100 years. We offer exceptional product performance and unparalleled support.
Learn More
Engineered Lumber
TJI® Joists
TimberStrand® LSL
Parallam® PSL
Microllam® LVL
Resources
Trus Joist Support
SturdiStep™ Stair Treads
RBS (Radiant Barrier Sheathing)
Roof & Wall Sheathing Plywood
Plywood
Doug Fir Larch Plywood
Southern Yellow Pine
Medium Density Fiberboard
MDF Product Specifications
MDF Sales and Distribution
Lumber
Energy
We're committed to clean, renewable options that meet environmental standards and coexist with sustainable forestry.
Learn More
Oil & Gas
Wind & Solar
Bioenergy
Sustainability
Sustainability
We're focused on climate change solutions, creating sustainable homes for everyone, and supporting thriving rural communities.
CEO Message
Our Strategy
Solid Foundation
Business Alignment
3 by 30 Positive Impact
Climate Change
Sustainable Homes
Rural Communities
Investors
For more than a hundred years, Weyerhaeuser has been building and enhancing a reputation for responsible corporate citizenship.
Learn More
Shareholder Center
Stock Information
Stock Quote
Interactive Chart
Historical Stock Price
Investment Calculator
Dividend Information
Careers
We offer a range of exciting career opportunities for smart, talented people who are passionate about making a difference.
Learn More
Who We Are
What We Do
Who We Need
What We Offer
Benefits
Growth and Development
Search Jobs
Search Internships
Manage Your Profile
Application Tips
Company
Company
We're working together to be the world’s premier timber, land, and forest products company.
Learn More
Vision & Values
Safety
Integrity
Sustainability
Inclusion
Citizenship
Giving Fund
Forestry
Sustainable ForestryForests in the Western U.S.
Forests in the Southern U.S.
Forests in the Northeastern U.S.
Forests in Canada
Log Sales
U.S. South Log Sales
U.S. West Log Sales
Seedling Sales
Southern Seedlings
Western Seedlings
About Our Seed and SeedlingsChristmas Tree Seedlings
Availability and Ordering
Planting & Care
Contact Western Seedlings
Recreation
Our ProgramsFind A Lease
Search LeasesLease FAQs
Campsite ProgramFood Plot ProgramSample LeasesNewslettersFind A PermitSearch PermitsPermit FAQsDisabled Hunter CompanionsSample PermitsResourcesState RegulationsNational OrganizationsContact UsLog InLandReal EstateDevelopment ProjectsMitigation BankingLouisianaCotton ValleyDenton BottomsLong LonesomeDolly TGum SwampMississippiTurkey CreekArkansasGreat BearNorth & South CarolinaBachelor's DelightBig Run (Pending)Brice CreekGeorgiaBroxton RocksFloridaSt. John's (Pending)MineralsAggregatesConservationWood ProductsEngineered LumberTJI® JoistsTJI® Joists for Eastern CanadaTimberStrand® LSLTimberStrand® LSL BeamsTimberStrand® LSL Framing LumberTimberStrand® LSL Rim BoardParallam® PSLParallam® PSL BeamsParallam® PSL ColumnsParallam® Plus PSLMicrollam® LVLMicrollam® LVL BeamsMicrollam® LVL HeadersResourcesTrus Joist SupportTJ-Pro™ RatingSatisfying Code for Fire Protection RequirementsNextPhase® Site SolutionsTrus Joist Floor Installation Video GuideLumberWestern LumberGreen StudsPremium Green Douglas-FirSPF MSR4-Square™ J-GradeNo Prior Select KD StudsSouthern LumberFramer Series™MSR & MELPremium™ JoistPro Series™3-Face ClearOSB & PanelsOriented Strand BoardDiamond™ Premium Floor PanelsEdge Gold™ Enhanced Floor PanelsThank YouEdge™ Floor PanelsSturdiStep™ Stair TreadsRBS (Radiant Barrier Sheathing)Roof & Wall SheathingPlywoodDoug Fir Larch PlywoodSouthern Yellow Pine PlywoodMedium Density FiberboardMDF Product SpecificationsMDF Sales and DistributionDistributionBuilding Green With WoodGreen BuildingResponsible Wood FiberProduct Stewardship & Safety Data SheetsSoftwareForte®WEB SoftwareJavelin® SoftwareStellar® SoftwareEstima® SoftwareOther SoftwareAutoCAD and SketchUp DownloadsRevit DownloadsDocument Library Mobile AppSoftware TrainingSoftware Training ScheduleWeyerhaeuser LearningDocument LibraryWhere to BuyBlogCanadaEnergyOil and GasWind and SolarBioenergySustainability
Our Strategy
Solid Foundation
Business Alignment
3 by 30 Positive Impact
Climate Change
Sustainable Homes
Rural Communities
Environmental Stewardship
Feedback
InvestorsCareersWho We AreWhat We DoWho We NeedWhere We WorkWhat We OfferPay and BenefitsGrowth & DevelopmentSearch JobsSearch Job OpeningsSearch InternshipsManage Your ProfileApplication TipsCompany
Vision & Values
Safety
Integrity
Sustainability
Inclusion
Citizenship
Giving Fund
Nominate a Volunteer
Effective Date: Jan. 1, 2020
This California Privacy Notice (“California Notice”) applies to “Consumers” as defined by the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) and supplements the Weyerhaeuser Privacy Policy . As used in this California Notice, references to “Weyerhaeuser,” “we,” “us,” or “our” include Weyerhaeuser Company and its affiliates, including Weyerhaeuser NR Company and Weyerhaeuser Company Limited. In the event of a conflict between this California Notice and any other Weyerhaeuser policy, statement, or notice, this California Notice will prevail as to California Consumers and their rights under the CCPA.
In accordance with the CCPA’s requirements, this California Notice covers calendar year 2019 and describes our online and offline practices regarding the Collection, use, disclosure and Sale of California Consumers’ Personal Information, and the rights California Consumers have regarding their Personal Information. We encourage you to read this California Notice and contact us with any questions.
Consistent with the CCPA, job applicants, current and former employees and contractors, and subjects of certain business-to-business communications acting solely in their capacity as representatives of another business, are not considered Consumers for purposes of this California Notice or the rights described herein.
Terms defined in the CCPA that are used in this California Notice (such as “Collect,” “Consumer,” “Personal Information,” “Sale,” and “Service Provider”) have the same meanings as in the CCPA.
COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Collection of Personal Information
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
RIGHT TO KNOW ABOUT PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED, DISCLOSED, OR SOLD
Instructions for Submitting a Request to Know
RIGHT TO REQUEST DELETION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Instructions for Submitting a Request to Delete
Exceptions to Request to Delete
RIGHT TO OPT-OUT OF THE SALE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION (AKA “DO NOT SELL”)
Instructions for Submitting a Request to Opt-Out
VERIFICATION PROCESS FOR CONSUMER REQUESTS
RESPONSE TIMING
NON-DISCRIMINATION
AUTHORIZED AGENTS
ACCESSIBILITY TO USERS WITH DISABILITIES
CONTACT FOR MORE INFORMATION
CHANGES TO THIS CALIFORNIA PRIVACY NOTICE
COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Collection of Personal Information
We Collect the following categories of Personal Information about California Consumers from the following sources for the following purposes:
Category of Personal Information Collected
Examples
(include but are not limited to the following)
Categories of Sources
Business or Commercial Purpose
Categories of Third-Party Recipients
Identifiers
Name, email, phone number, postal address, IP address, or other similar identifiers
Consumer
(e.g., directly from you or from your activity on our website)
Service Providers
Business partners
(e.g., builders and dealers)
To provide and improve our products and services, and to otherwise communicate with you
Service Providers
Business partners
Government entities
Customer records
Name, signature, postal address and phone number
Consumer
Service Providers
Business partners
To facilitate the delivery of our products and services, and to support billing and collection
Service Providers
Business partners
Government entities
Commercial information
Records of products purchased
Consumer
Service Providers
Business partners
To provide and improve our products and services, for marketing purposes, and to support billing and collection
Service Providers
Business partners
Internet or network activity
Activity on our websites, including pages visited
Consumer
Service Providers
To provide and improve our websites, products and services, for marketing purposes, and to enhance Consumers’ experiences
Service Providers
Internet service providers
Data analytics providers
Business partners
Geolocation data
Browser location
Consumer
To provide and improve our websites, products and services, and for marketing purposes
Service Providers
Sensory data
Recordings of customer service calls and voicemails
Security camera footage
Consumer
To provide and improve our products and services, research and resolve issues, improve Consumers’ experiences, and for safety and security
Service Providers
Professional or employment-related information
Your employer information
Consumer
To provide our products and services, and to support billing and collection
Service Providers
Business partners
In addition to the foregoing, we may Collect, use, and disclose your Personal Information as required or permitted by applicable law, and for detecting security incidents and protecting against fraud and illegal activity. We do not treat Deidentified data or Aggregate Consumer Information as Personal Information, and we reserve the right to convert, or permit others to convert, your Personal Information into Deidentified data or Aggregate Consumer Information.
Subject to the CCPA’s restrictions and obligations, our affiliates, Service Providers, and vendors may use your Personal Information for the above-listed business purposes.
We may Collect, use, and share your Personal Information with our Service Providers and vendors (including those that facilitate interest-based advertising and other advertising and marketing) in a manner that may be deemed a Sale under the CCPA. For more information on how to exercise your “Do Not Sell” rights, see “Right to Opt-Out of the Sale of Personal Information” below.
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
Under the CCPA, California Consumers have certain rights that they may exercise independently or through an authorized agent. CCPA rights requests are subject to an identification and verification process. We will not fulfill a CCPA request unless we have been provided enough information for us to reasonably verify that the requestor is the Consumer about whom we collected Personal Information.
Some Personal Information we maintain about Consumers (e.g., clickstream data) is not sufficiently associated with enough other Personal Information for us to be able to verify it to any individual Consumer. Accordingly, we will not include such information in response to a Consumer CCPA request.
If we cannot comply with a request, we will explain the reasons in our response. We will use Personal Information provided in your request only to verify your identity or authority to make the request and to track and document request responses, unless you also provided the Personal Information to us for another purpose.
We are not obligated to comply with Consumer requests to the extent that doing so would infringe on our or any other person’s rights, or conflict with applicable law.
RIGHT TO KNOW ABOUT PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED, DISCLOSED, OR SOLD
Under the CCPA, a Consumer has the right to request that we disclose what Personal Information we have Collected, used, disclosed, and Sold (a “Request to Know”). A Consumer may submit a Request to Know no more than twice in any 12-month period.
If you submit a verifiable Request to Know, we will provide the following information to you, with respect to the 12-month period preceding our receipt of your request:
the categories of Personal Information we have Collected about you;
the categories of sources from which we Collected the Personal Information about you;
our business or commercial purpose for Collecting or Selling Personal Information;
the categories of third parties with whom we shared your Personal Information;
the specific pieces of Personal Information we Collected about you; and
if we Sold or disclosed your Personal Information for a business purpose,
the categories of Personal Information that we Sold about you and the categories of third parties to whom we Sold the Personal Information; and
the categories of Personal Information that we disclosed about you for a business purpose.
Instructions for Submitting a Request to Know
You may submit a Request to Know by visiting our CCPA Requests webpage , clicking on the “Submit Privacy Request” link, and completing the information on the webform. Alternatively, you may call our privacy hotline tollfree at (844) 330-7632. We encourage you to review our FAQs before filling out the form and submitting your request. We recommend that you keep a copy of the FAQs open to refer to when filling out the form.
RIGHT TO REQUEST DELETION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Under California law, a Consumer has the right to request that we delete any Personal Information that we have Collected from you (a “Request to Delete”).
Instructions for Submitting a Request to Delete
You may submit a Request to Delete by visiting our CCPA Requests webpage , clicking on the “Submit Privacy Request” link, and completing the information on the webform. Alternatively, you may call our privacy hotline tollfree at (844) 330-7632. We encourage you to review our FAQs before filling out the form and submitting your request. We recommend that you keep a copy of the FAQs open to refer to when filling out the form.
Exceptions to Request to Delete
Under the CCPA, we may deny your Request to Delete if retaining the Personal Information is necessary for us (or our Service Providers) to do any of the following:
complete the transaction for which we collected the Personal Information, provide a good or service that you requested, or take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship;
comply with a legal obligation;
detect security incidents and protect against fraud;
enable internal uses that are reasonably aligned with Consumer expectations based on your relationship with us;
make other internal and lawful uses of that Personal Information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it;
debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality;
exercise free speech or exercise another right provided for by law;
comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 seq.); or
engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest.
RIGHT TO OPT-OUT OF THE SALE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION (AKA “DO NOT SELL”)
Under the CCPA, a Consumer has the right to opt out of the Sale of your Personal Information collected or maintained by us (a “Request to Opt-Out”). A Request to Opt-Out encompasses the right to direct us to stop Selling your Personal Information (to the extent that we currently do so) and to refrain from doing so in the future.
Instructions for Submitting a Request to Opt-Out
You may submit a Request to Opt-Out by visiting our CCPA Requests webpage, clicking on the “Submit ‘Do Not Sell’ Request” link, and completing the information on the webform. Alternatively, you may call our privacy hotline tollfree at (844) 330-7632. We encourage you to review our FAQs before filling out the form and submitting your request. We recommend that you keep a copy of the FAQs open to refer to when filling out the form.
If you use an authorized agent to exercise your Request to Opt-Out, you will need to provide proof of the authorization. See below under “Authorized Agents”.
We use third-party cookies and tracking technologies to collect data when you visit our websites and mobile apps. There is not yet consensus as to whether these third-party cookies and tracking technologies associated with our websites constitute a Sale of Personal Information; however, we do not currently consider this activity to be a Sale. If you want to exercise control over cookies and tracking technologies associated with our websites, rather than providing us a “Request to Opt-Out” as described above, you can adjust the settings on your browser to remove or limit cookies. Mobile devices may offer other ad and data limitation choices. Please be aware that changing settings on your browser or clearing cookies may affect the availability or functionality of our websites. Also, because browser settings are unique to each browser, you may have to opt-out separately via each browser and other device you use. In addition, third-party tools may enable you to search for and opt-out of some of these trackers, such as the Digital Advertising Alliance and the Network Advertising Initiative. We make no representations about these third-party tools, programs or statements.
Some browsers have signals that may be characterized as “Do Not Track” or “DNT” signals.  Like many websites, our websites are not designed to respond to "Do Not Track" signals received from browsers. Accordingly, we currently do not recognize these “Do Not Track” signals as a “Request to Opt-Out.” To learn more about "DNT" please visit https://allaboutdnt.com.
We do not knowingly Collect or Sell the Personal Information of minors under 16 years of age without affirmative authorization.
We may disclose your Personal Information for the following purposes, which are not considered a Sale: (i) if you direct us to share Personal Information; (ii) to comply with your requests under the CCPA; (iii) disclosures among the entities that constitute Weyerhaeuser  as defined above, or as part of a merger or asset sale; and (iv) as otherwise required or permitted by applicable law.
VERIFICATION PROCESS FOR CONSUMER REQUESTS
Before we can complete your Request to Know or Request to Delete, we will need to verify your identity. We describe our verification process below:
When you submit your request, you will be asked to identify your relationship to Weyerhaeuser.
We will confirm receipt of your request, and at that time we will request that you provide information or documentation to us to confirm your identity. We will request that you provide specific information related to your stated relationship with Weyerhaeuser. For example, if you are a customer, we may request that you provide information about your most recent purchase, or if you are a Recreational Lease Holder, we may request that you provide information about your lease. The information you provide must match a minimum number of data points with information that we maintain and that we consider reliable for purposes of verification.
Whenever feasible, we will seek to match the identifying information provided by you to the personal information that we already maintain.
We will review the information provided by you. If we cannot verify your identity from the information we already maintain, we may request additional information. We will use such additional information only for the purposes of verifying your identity and for security or fraud-prevention purposes. We will delete any new Personal Information collected for the purposes of verification as soon as practical after processing the request, except as required by applicable law.
We may also require that you provide a signed declaration under penalty of perjury that you are the Consumer whose Personal Information is the subject of the request.
If we cannot reasonably verify that the person making the request is the Consumer about whom we have Collected Personal Information, we will state that in our response to you and will provide an explanation.
RESPONSE TIMING
We will endeavor to respond to a verifiable Request to Know or Request to Delete within 45 days of our receipt of the request. If we require more time (up to an additional 45 days), we will inform you of the reason.  Upon receiving a Request to Opt-Out, we will act upon the request as soon as feasibly possible, but no later than 15 days from the date we receive the request.
NON-DISCRIMINATION
We will not discriminate against you or treat you adversely for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not:
deny you goods or services;
charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including using discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties;
provide you a different level or quality of goods or services; or
suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.
AUTHORIZED AGENTS
A Consumer can designate an authorized agent, who is either a natural person or a business entity registered with the California Secretary of State, to make a Request to Know, Request to Delete or Request to Opt-Out on the Consumer’s behalf, by one of the following:
Power of Attorney – A power of attorney that complies with California Probate Code sections 4000 to 4465, authorizing the agent as the Consumer’s attorney in fact; or
Explicit Written Consent – A document signed by the Consumer and notarized by a notary public, stating that the agent is authorized to act on behalf of the Consumer, authorizing the specific request to Weyerhaeuser and expressly consenting to Weyerhaeuser providing the requested information to the agent or taking the requested action.
A parent or guardian may also make a verifiable Consumer request on behalf of his or her minor child.
When a Consumer uses an authorized agent to submit a Request to Know, Request to Delete or Request to Opt-Out, we may require a copy of the Explicit Written Consent or the Power of Attorney. Additionally, if we receive a copy of the Explicit Written Consent, we may also require that the Consumer verify his or her own identity directly with us.
We may deny a request from an agent that does not submit proof that they have been authorized by the Consumer to act on his or her behalf.
ACCESSIBILITY TO USERS WITH DISABILITIES
This California Notice is accessible to users with disabilities, including keyboard-only users and those with visual impairments. Users with visual impairments can use a screen reader to learn more information on our California privacy practices. A list of available screen readers can be found by searching the Internet, including the website for the National Library Service for the Blind and Print Disabled.
OTHER CALIFORNIA NOTICES
California’s “Shine the Light” law permits California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes.
We do not share Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes without either obtaining your consent or giving you the ability to opt-out. If you are a California resident, you may request information about our compliance with the Shine the Light law by contacting us at privacy@weyerhaeuser.com or by sending a letter to 220 Occidental Ave. S., Seattle, WA 98104, Attention: Privacy - Legal Department. Any such request must include “California Shine the Light Privacy Rights Request” in the first line of the description and include your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this email address or mail address.
Please note that “Shine the Light” rights and CCPA rights are established under different legal regimes and must be exercised separately.
CONTACT FOR MORE INFORMATION
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies and practices, you may contact us by email at privacy@weyerhaeuser.com, by phone at (844) 330-7632, or by mail at the following address:
Weyerhaeuser Company
220 Occidental Ave. S.
Seattle, WA 98104
Attn: Privacy - Legal Department
CHANGES TO THIS CALIFORNIA PRIVACY NOTICE
We will update this California Notice at least annually, and we may update it more frequently if our practices materially change. When we make changes to this California Notice, we will post a notice on our website homepage and we will update the date at the top of this California Notice.
Connect with us
By using this website, you agree to our Privacy Policy. California residents: See our CCPA Privacy Notice for details on what personal information we collect and for what purposes.
